trustedproperties.com 2010-03-27

# Trusted Properties

**Introduction**

www.Trustedproperties.com is a web site of Trustedproperties KPO Private Limited ("We", "our" and "us" in this Privacy Policy). By using this site ("the web site"), you agree to the Internet Privacy Policy set out below. This Internet Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through your conduct on the web site. 

When you provide personal information to the web site, the data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 is Trusted properties KPO Pvt. Ltd. the registered address for which is No:392 & 393 Rajiv Gandhi Salai, OMR , Kotivakkam, Chennai:600041. 

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This Internet Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site. We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the web site. 

We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our sites, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual ("personal information"). This Internet Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with. This Internet Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. We welcome your comments and feedback. 

**What information about you do we collect?**

We may collect and process the following personal information about you: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on the web site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use the web site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information if you report a problem with our site. 
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 
  * Details of transactions you carry out through the web site. 
  * Details of your visits to the web site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data and the resources that you access. 

It is our intention that this policy will protect your information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in India. 

**How we use your information**

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To provide a better service to you, for instance by automatically populating forms on the website by which you make enquiries of selected estate agents 
  * To provide you with service information, products or services that you request from us 
  * Subject to your expressed preferences and/or information we give you at the time that your information becomes available to us, (1) to provide you with information about offers, promotions, goods or services of ours and of other businesses which we believe may be of interest to you and (2) sharing your information with our service providers and other third parties so that they and others can contact you direct about their offers, promotions, goods or services. 
  * To help carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us. 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so. 
  * To notify you about changes to our service and remind you of your password and username. 

If you wish to opt out of receiving any marketing materials from us or our service providers and agents, you may unsubscribe at any time from our marketing communications by logging in to the site. 

**Real estate agents**

You should be aware that providing information to an estate agent through our web site will result in the information being passed to the estate agent and what they then do with your information will be their responsibility, not ours and they will hold your information subject to any privacy policy of that estate agent, which may not conform with this Internet Privacy Policy. 

**Disclosure**

Apart from the disclosures to third parties described in the "How we use your information" section above or where you have separately consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, we may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure. 

We may engage third parties to provide you with goods or services on our behalf. In that circumstance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties in order to meet your request for goods or services. 

**Security**

We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. 

However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also use all reasonable endeavours to ensure its security on our systems. 

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we are not responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. 

We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep accurate and up to date any information which we hold about you. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you should contact us to have the information corrected. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are data that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are industry standard and are used by most web sites, including those operated by us, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to customise the web site to your needs. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. However, you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with some features of our on-line services. 

**Links to Other Sites**

We will provide links to web sites outside of our web site, as well as to third party web sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to our web site. Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that web site and its privacy statement. 

**Problems or Questions**

If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our web site, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, Please contact us. 

**Further Data Protection Information**

For more information about data protection issues in the India and protecting your privacy, visit the website of the Information.
